http://www.gsw.edu/legal

The browser you are using is out of date and may not support all of the features of this website. Please update your browser to a modern browser that supports HTML5.
About
A-Z index
Map
Search
APPLY
VISIT
PROGRAMS
GIVE
Main Menu
AcademicsAcademicsColleges and DepartmentsDistance LearningDegree ProgramsCurriculum SheetsRegistrar's OfficeAcademic ResourcesAcademic AffairsInstitutional ResearchCourse Schedule ArchiveFAQAdmissionsAdmissionsUndergraduate AdmissionsGraduate AdmissionsGeneral InformationApply to GSWWho Are You?Visit GSWImmunization InformationFinancial AidFinancial AidIntroductionTuition and FeesGSW AffordabilityStaff and Contact InfoFreshman ChecklistApplication for Federal Student AidSatisfactory Academic ProgressGrantsScholarshipsLoansWork StudyCheck Financial Aid StatusWhat Happens If I Withdraw?FormsConsumer's Right to KnowImportant TermsFAQNewsflash AthleticsAthleticsBaseballMen's BasketballWomen's BasketballCross CountryGolfMen's SoccerWomen's SoccerSoftballWomen's TennisMen's Cross CountryCampus LifeCampus LifeCampus LivingCampus ServicesStudent ActivitiesResources and InformationDivision of Student Engagement and SuccessGSW Public Safety CalendarsCalendarsAcademic CalendarAcademic Affairs CalendarAdmissions CalendarRegistration ScheduleACCUPLACER Testing ScheduleFinal Examination ScheduleHoliday ScheduleArt Gallery ScheduleCampus Events
Legal & Privacy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy sets forth Georgia Southwestern State University policy with respect to the gathering and dissemination of information we obtain from you on the web site for Georgia Southwestern State University located at gsw.edu (“Site”).
Georgia Southwestern State University is the operator of this Site, although software, hosting and other functions may be provided by third parties (“Service Providers”). This Privacy Policy describes the type of information Georgia Southwestern State University and its Service Providers collect from visitors to this Site, what we do with that information, and how visitors can update and control the use of information provided on this Site. This policy does not necessarily describe information collection policies on other sites, such as separate sites operated by our Service Providers that we do not control. Many of the resources linked from this Web site are not maintained by Georgia Southwestern State University. Georgia Southwestern State University cannot monitor all linked resources, only those pages which fall directly within Georgia Southwestern State University world-wide web structure. Georgia Southwestern State University is in no way responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these linked resources and the statements, views, and opinions expressed therein are neither endorsed by nor do they necessarily reflect the opinion of Georgia Southwestern State University.
This policy may be changed from time to time and without further notice. Your continued use of the Site after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new terms. If you do not agree to abide by these new terms or any future terms, please do not use the Site. This site is not directed to children under 13 years of age, and children under 13 years of age shall not use this Site to submit any personal information about themselves.
Information We Gather
When you visit the Site, we may collect certain routing information, including, but not limited to, the Internet Protocol address of your originating Internet Service Provider, and information provided by “cookies” stored on your hard drive. We may also collect aggregate information about the use of the Site, including, but not limited to, which pages are most frequently visited, how many visitors we receive daily, and how long visitors stay on each page. We may disclose and publish aggregate information on an aggregate basis to any party through any means, but such aggregate information will not disclose any personal information. Any information collected through this Site may also be used in aggregate by system administrators in the administration of the Site. You may be required to provide certain personal information in order to access various features and information on the Site. Such information may include, among other things, your name, address, and phone number. If you do not want to provide such information, you may choose not to access those features of the Site. Any personal information that you choose to provide through the Site will be protected in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.
Cookies
Cookies are small pieces of data that may be stored by a Web browser. Cookies are often used to remember information about preferences and pages you have visited. For example, when you visit some sites on the Web you might see a “Welcome Back” message. The first time you visited the site a cookie may have been set on your computer; when you return, the cookie is read again. You can refuse to accept cookies, can disable cookies, and remove cookies from your hard drive. However, if you do not accept cookies from the Site, you may lose access to the Site or experience decreased performance of the Site.
Security and Accuracy of Confidential Information
Georgia Southwestern State University does its best to ensure that the personal information obtained from you is accurate. You may review the information saved or submitted via the Site at any time up to the point when it is purged from the flat file or database. In the event that there is an error in your personal information, we will correct the information on your request.
While we strive to protect your personal information by encryption and other means, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of the information you transmit to us, and if you choose to use the Site, you do so at your own risk.
Please keep in mind that the information disclosed by you on our Site in certain forums – for example, information, including personal information, that you may provide to others on bulletin boards, through blogs or in chat rooms that may be available on the Site – can be collected and used by visitors to the Site.
Sharing of Information
Georgia Southwestern State University is committed to maintaining the privacy and accuracy of your personal information. We do not actively share personal information gathered from the Site. However, some information collected from the Site may be subject to the Georgia Open Records Act. This means that while we do not actively share information, in some cases we may be compelled by law to release information gathered from the Site. Georgia public universities also comply with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), which prohibits the release of education records without student permission. For more details on FERPA, currently enrolled students should see the catalog.
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics to help Analyse how users use the site. The tool uses "cookies," which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors' us of the webiste and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Georgia Southwestern State University.
We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.
You may choose to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically default to accept them, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.
User’s Personal Information: Visitors to our website may be able to register to use our services, attend events, make a purchase, join a community or upload/download information. When you register, you will provide personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number and other relevant information. If you are making a purchase, we will request financial information including your credit card number, expiration date, and security code. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for your purchase. This information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary, including: To fulfill your requests, to protect ourselves from liability, to comply with the terms and conditions of our internet host provider.
EULA for Mobile Applications
GSW Mobile Copyright (c) 2014 Georgia Southwestern State University
*** END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT ***
IMPORTANT: PLEASE READ THIS LICENSE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SOFTWARE.
1. LICENSE
By receiving, opening the file package, and/or using GSW Mobile ("Software") containing this software, you agree that this End User User License Agreement (EULA) is a legally binding and valid contract and agree to be bound by it. You agree to abide by the intellectual property laws and all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
Unless you have a different license agreement signed by Georgia Southwestern State University your use of GSW Mobile indicates your acceptance of this license agreement and warranty.
Subject to the terms of this Agreement, Georgia Southwestern State University grants to you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable license, without right to sub-license, to use GSW Mobile in accordance with this Agreement and any other written agreement with Georgia Southwestern State University. Georgia Southwestern State University does not transfer the title of GSW Mobile to you; the license granted to you is not a sale. This agreement is a binding legal agreement between Georgia Southwestern State University and the purchasers or users of GSW Mobile.
If you do not agree to be bound by this agreement, remove GSW Mobile from your computer now and, if applicable, promptly return to Georgia Southwestern State University by mail any copies of GSW Mobile and related documentation and packaging in your possession.
2. DISTRIBUTION
GSW Mobile and the license herein granted shall not be copied, shared, distributed, re-sold, offered for re-sale, transferred or sub-licensed in whole or in part except that you may make one copy for archive purposes only. For information about redistribution of GSW Mobile contact Georgia Southwestern State University.
3. USER AGREEMENT
3.1 Use
Your license to use GSW Mobile is limited to the number of licenses purchased by you. You shall not allow others to use, copy or evaluate copies of GSW Mobile.
3.2 Use Restrictions
You shall use GSW Mobile in compliance with all applicable laws and not for any unlawful purpose. Without limiting the foregoing, use, display or distribution of GSW Mobile together with material that is pornographic, racist, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, libelous, abusive, promoting hatred, discriminating or displaying prejudice based on religion, ethnic heritage, race, sexual orientation or age is strictly prohibited.
Each licensed copy of GSW Mobile may be used on one single computer location by one user. Use of GSW Mobile means that you have loaded, installed, or run GSW Mobile on a computer or similar device. If you install GSW Mobile onto a multi-user platform, server or network, each and every individual user of GSW Mobile must be licensed separately.
You may make one copy of GSW Mobile for backup purposes, providing you only have one copy installed on one computer being used by one person. Other users may not use your copy of GSW Mobile . The assignment, sublicense, networking, sale, or distribution of copies of GSW Mobile are strictly forbidden without the prior written consent of Georgia Southwestern State University. It is a violation of this agreement to assign, sell, share, loan, rent, lease, borrow, network or transfer the use of GSW Mobile. If any person other than yourself uses GSW Mobile registered in your name, regardless of whether it is at the same time or different times, then this agreement is being violated and you are responsible for that violation!
3.3 Copyright Restriction
This Software contains copyrighted material, trade secrets and other proprietary material. You shall not, and shall not attempt to, modify, reverse engineer, disassemble or decompile GSW Mobile. Nor can you create any derivative works or other works that are based upon or derived from GSW Mobile in whole or in part.
Georgia Southwestern State University's name, logo and graphics file that represents GSW Mobile shall not be used in any way to promote products developed with GSW Mobile . Georgia Southwestern State University retains sole and exclusive ownership of all right, title and interest in and to GSW Mobile and all Intellectual Property rights relating thereto.
Copyright law and international copyright treaty provisions protect all parts of GSW Mobile, products and services. No program, code, part, image, audio sample, or text may be copied or used in any way by the user except as intended within the bounds of the single user program. All rights not expressly granted hereunder are reserved for Georgia Southwestern State University.
3.4 Limitation of Responsibility
You will indemnify, hold harmless, and defend Georgia Southwestern State University , its employees, agents and distributors against any and all claims, proceedings, demand and costs resulting from or in any way connected with your use of Georgia Southwestern State University's Software.
In no event (including, without limitation, in the event of negligence) will Georgia Southwestern State University , its employees, agents or distributors be liable for any consequential, incidental, indirect, special or punitive damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, loss of use, business interruption, loss of information or data, or pecuniary loss), in connection with or arising out of or related to this Agreement, GSW Mobile or the use or inability to use GSW Mobile or the furnishing, performance or use of any other matters hereunder whether based upon contract, tort or any other theory including negligence.
Georgia Southwestern State University's entire liability, without exception, is limited to the customers' reimbursement of the purchase price of the Software (maximum being the lesser of the amount paid by you and the suggested retail price as listed by Georgia Southwestern State University ) in exchange for the return of the product, all copies, registration papers and manuals, and all materials that constitute a transfer of license from the customer back to Georgia Southwestern State University.
3.5 Warranties
Except as expressly stated in writing, Georgia Southwestern State University makes no representation or warranties in respect of this Software and expressly excludes all other warranties, expressed or implied, oral or written, including, without limitation, any implied warranties of merchantable quality or fitness for a particular purpose.
3.6 Governing Law
This Agreement shall be governed by the law of the United States applicable therein. You hereby irrevocably attorn and submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of United States therefrom. If any provision shall be considered unlawful, void or otherwise unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this License and not affect the validity and enforceability of any other provisions.
3.7 Termination
Any failure to comply with the terms and conditions of this Agreement will result in automatic and immediate termination of this license. Upon termination of this license granted herein for any reason, you agree to immediately cease use of GSW Mobile and destroy all copies of GSW Mobile supplied under this Agreement. The financial obligations incurred by you shall survive the expiration or termination of this license.
4. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY
THIS SOFTWARE AND THE ACCOMPANYING FILES ARE SOLD "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES AS TO PERFORMANCE OR MERCHANTABILITY OR ANY OTHER WARRANTIES WHETHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED. THIS DISCLAIMER CONCERNS ALL FILES GENERATED AND EDITED BY GSW Mobile AS WELL.
5. CONSENT OF USE OF DATA
You agree that Georgia Southwestern State University may collect and use information gathered in any manner as part of the product support services provided to you, if any, related to GSW Mobile.Georgia Southwestern State University may also use this information to provide notices to you which may be of use or interest to you.
6. Termination of Service
The online services required to use this application and any related sources can be terminated at any time.  There is no guarantee of availability and no support provided.  The app does require the server in order to operate and the server may be taken offline at any time for maintenance or permanently.
GSW Website Search
×
Email Access
To login into email, please select from the following:
GSW Email (O365)    Manage Spam Quarantine (Employees)    Old Student Email (Gmail)   Email Help
×
Apply to GSW
Thank you for your interest in Georgia Southwestern. What would you like to apply for?
Undergraduate Admissions    Graduate Admissions    Check Admission Status
×
D2L Access
To login into D2L, please select GeorgiaView or GoView option
GeorgiaView    GoView
×
Site Login
You can use this portal to login to the GSW website.  This will allow you to make instant edits to your pages. If you do not have an account and are a GSW Faculty/Staff member please click here.Please be sure to logout when you are done!
Username
Password
Remember Me
Log in
Create an account
Forgot your username?
Forgot your password?
×
CanesNet Account
Please select a password reset process:
Legacy Student Reset Process   GSW Account Reset
×
CanesNet Account
Set up CanesNet passwordMy password is expiring (change password)I forgot my password (reset password)What is CanesNet?
University Drive,
Americus, Georgia 31709
(877) 871-4594
Contact UsGSW Mobile AppEmployee Self-ServiceCareersLegal & PrivacyDisclaimerText OnlyHuman Trafficking NoticeEthics Reporting HotlineTitle IX
Beacon Canes Connect GeorgiaVIEW/GoVIEWEmailRAINClass ScheduleTechnical Support PortalCanesNet AccountWebsite Login
#TakeTomorrowByStorm
